Oh in my head
You said with certainty
I may be the dumbest person
that you’ve ever seen
You think you’re hurting me
Betcha won’t believe it
But you kinda set me free
You’ve mentioned Adderall
Slip this guy a sedative
He’s bouncing off the wall
Honey it’s no big deal
We’ll getcha back to college
You could study something real
So if that’s how you feel
When we go down
When kingdom come
Don’t look at me
I’m just too dumb
I’d love to stay
But like you said
Don't look at me
Cause I've got nothing in my head
Oh in my head
Too dumb for breaking up
I’d do it in person
but I’d probably mess it up
I’ll text you, that’s enough
That’s how empty-headed people
Get through shitty stuff
Your world is ending soon
Mine’s a little better cause
I never watch the news
You make my lunch today
I would do it
but I couldn’t work my microwave
So if that’s what you’re saying
When we go down
When kingdom come
Don’t look at me
I’m just too dumb
I'd love to stay
But like you said
Don't look at me
Cause I got nothing in my head
Oh in my head
You should not have done that
Da da da da da da
When we go down
When kingdom come
Don't look at me
I'm much too dumb
I'd love to stay
But like you said
Don't look at me
Cause I got nothing in my head
Oh in my head
When we go down
When kingdom come
Don't look at me
I’m just too dumb